maxcheaters.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy - MaxCheaters.com | Lineage 2 Development Marketplace Bots and Cheats

Thanks for visiting MaxCheaters.com Privacy Policy. We’re updating our Policy as of **May 25, 2018**. Here are some of the changes you’ll see: 

We’ve updated the Policy to reflect changes in data privacy laws.  
We’ve added details about your ability to manage the information you share with us, and the new tools we’ve created to help you do that.  
This updated Policy gives you more control over your information and more clearly explains how we use it. 

**Changes to This Policy**  
We may update this Policy from time to time. If we do, we’ll let you know about any material changes, either by notifying you on the Site or by sending you an email. New versions of this Policy will never apply retroactively — we’ll tell you the exact date they go into effect. If you keep using MaxCheaters after a change, that means you accept this Policy. 

**Who We Are**  
MaxCheaters is community platform,which provides our members the oportunity to communicate for common interests such as multiplayer online gaming, developing, desiging, cheating and more. (we are not responsible for 3rd party topics/threads/posts , but we will comply if something is against our rules). We are a team of enthusiasts for online roleplaying gaming. 

**How This Policy Applies**  
This Policy describes the information we collect from you, how we use that information and our legal basis for doing so. It also covers whether and how that information may be shared and your rights and choices regarding the information you provide to us. If you see a capitalized word, it’s defined in our Terms of Use. We use cookies and similar technologies, as described in our Cookie Policy. 

By using the Services offered by MaxCheaters, you’re acknowledging you have agreed to our Terms of Use and that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and our Cookie Policy. 

**What We Collect and Receive**  
In order for you to create an account on MaxCheaters and use our Services, we need to collect and process certain information. Depending on your use of the Services, that may include: 

Information you provide by completing forms on MaxCheaters — your **username** , **email** , **country** of residence, **gender** , **login** , and **password** details. We may ask for this information if you register as a user of the Services, subscribe to our newsletters, upload or submit content through MaxCheaters, or if you contact us;  
Information you provide  when posting/making a topic including your username,,country of residence ;  
Details of any requests or transactions you make through the Services. MaxCheaters partners with other companies (such as PayPal) for payment processing, and the payment information you submit is collected and used by them in accordance with their privacy policies. MaxCheaters doesn’t store your payment information apart from your PayPal email address for security purposes;  
Information about your activity on and interaction with MaxCheaters, including use of our mobile apps (such as your **IP address** , the type of **device** or **browser** you use, and your actions on the Site);  
Information about the ways people visit and interact with our Site, in the form of traffic analytics. You can opt out of being included in Google Analytics here. For more information about our use of data analytics to protect and improve our Services, see our Cookie Policy;  
Communications you send to us (for example, when you ask for support, send us questions or comments, or report a problem);  
Information that you submit on or to MaxCheaters in the form of topics, posts, comments, contributions to discussions, or messages to other users; The email address associated with your Facebook account, if you choose to sign up using your Facebook credentials. MaxCheaters will also request permission to access your name, profile picture, and friend list (these permissions are governed by Facebook’s privacy policies and can be managed through your Facebook privacy settings). We never post anything to your Facebook, Twitter, or other third-party accounts without your permission.  
You may decline to provide us with your information. However, this will limit your ability to register for an account or use our Services. You may review, change or remove your information through your account settings. 

**What We NEVER Collect and Receive**

MaxCheaters will never ask for your realname, surname,(we use username instead) , home address (country is requested only) , phone number , personal ID, driver licence or any other kind of personal information. If any of these kind of information is shared anywhere in community by 3rd party members, must be reported and deleted immediately by our staffers team. Contact at admin@maxcheaters.com or send a support request. 

**How We Use This Information**  
We use the information we collect for the following purposes: 

To keep your account secure and protect our Services (including to verify the identities of creators and prevent fraud and abuse);  
To enable us to provide you with our Services, and to improve and promote our Services;  
To create and administer your account, contact you, and customize your experience on MaxCheaters ;  
To track and analyze use of the Services so that we can improve how MaxCheaters is performing and provide users with the best experience possible. 

**European Union Users**  
Data protection law in Europe requires a “lawful basis” for collecting and retaining personal information from citizens or residents of the European Economic Area. Our lawful bases include:  
Legitimate interests: This is a technical term in data protection law which essentially means we have a good and fair reason to use your data and we do so in ways which do not hurt your interests and rights. We sometimes require your data to pursue our legitimate interests in a way that might reasonably be expected as part of running our business and that does not materially impact your rights, freedom or interests. 

For example, we use username, email, device, and location information to prevent fraud and abuse and to keep the Services secure. We may also send you promotional communications about our Services, subject to your right to control whether we do so. 

We analyze how users interact with our Site so we can understand better what elements of the design are working well and which are not working so well. This allows us to improve and develop the quality of the online experience we offer all our users. 

**How This Information Is Shared**  
Information that’s shared publicly  
When you create an account, we create a basic profile page for you on MaxCheaters, containing your username, the date the account was created, and a list of topics / posts you may have. By default, your email is private. Your username appears with the topics you make and posts you send on MaxCheaters and, if your profile has enabled to view visitors, people can click your username to view visitors history also. 

Other members will be able to see the following things: 

The account username you select, and the date the account was created;  
Any information you choose to add to your profile (like a picture,gender, bio,signature or your country);  
Topics you have made;  
Posts and replies you have made;  
Comments you’ve posted on profile; 

Profile feedback;  
You can modify or delete certain information associated with your account (such as your displayname, profile image, biography and country) from your account settings, and you can change your privacy settings if you want to make your profile private or adjust the default settings. 

**Information that isn’t shared publicly**  
The following data will not be publicly displayed or revealed to other users: 

Any payment information you provide;  
Your password details;  
Your IP address;  
Your email;  
Communications you send to us (for example, when you ask for support, send us questions or comments, or report a problem). 

**Information that’s shared to protect MaxCheaters and comply with the law**  
We do reserve the right to disclose personal information when we believe that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with the law or law enforcement, to prevent fraud or abuse, or to protect MaxCheaters legal rights, property, or the safety of Maxcheaters, its staffers, users, or others. 

**Links to other websites and services**  
Our Site may include links to other websites or services whose privacy practices may differ from Maxcheaters. When you use a link to an external site or service, the privacy policy and data processing disclosures for that site or service governs. 

**Retention**  
We will retain your information as long as your account is active, as necessary to provide you with the Services or as otherwise set forth in this Policy. We will also retain and use this information as necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy and to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements and protect Maxcheaters legal rights. 

We also collect and maintain aggregated, anonymized or pseudonymized information which we may retain indefinitely to protect the safety and security of our Site, improve our Services or comply with legal obligations. 

**Your Rights**  
Users residing in certain countries, including the EU, are afforded certain rights regarding their personal information. Except where an exception or exemption applies, these rights include the ability to access, correct, and request deletion of your personal information. While these rights are not applicable globally, all Maxcheaters users can manage their personal information, as further described below, in their account settings. 

To modify or delete the personal information you’ve provided to us, please log in and update your profile. You may also request to delete your account by sending an email to admin@maxcheaters.com. We may retain certain information as required by law or as necessary for our legitimate business purposes. Deleted account's topics/posts may retain anonymously by author "deleted account". 

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**Cookies**

This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.
